Alvin and the Chipmunks Meet the Wolfman is a family,
fantasy, comedy film directed by Kathi Castillo.
As Alvin struggles with nightmares involving werewolves, the school play of
Jekyll & Hyde is in jeopardy when the lead, Alvin, is suspended.
In an attempt to boost his confidence, the principal suggests
Theodore, who's suddenly going through some canine changes.
Alvin Seville / Simon Seville / Dave Seville
(voice), played by Ross Bagdasarian, Jr..
Theodore / Brittany / Jeanette / Eleanor (voice), played by Janice Karman.
Mr. Lawrence Talbot (voice), played by Maurice LaMarche.
Principal Milliken (voice), played by Miriam Flynn.
Mr. Rochelle (voice), played by Rob Paulsen.
Madame Raya (voice), played by April Winchell.
Alvin and the Chipmunks Meet the Wolfman is a 2000 American animated musical comedy horror film produced by
Bagdasarian Productions and Universal Cartoon Studios and based on characters from Alvin and the Chipmunks.
It is the second Alvin and the Chipmunks direct-to-video film following Alvin and the Chipmunks Meet Frankenstein, and the
third of three Universal Cartoon Studios productions to be animated overseas by Tama Productions in Tokyo, Japan.
The film introduces the voices of Maurice LaMarche and Miriam Flynn.
This was the final Alvin and the Chipmunks
production to be traditionally animated.
The film explores themes of fortune teller, single
parent, cartoon, full moon, musical.
The tone is lighthearted.